Finding Aid for President (University of Michigan) records, 1967-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files 1967/68-2008/09
  - 1980-1981
    - Carillonneur (Box 118)
    - Centers (Box 118)
    - Clements Library (Box 118)
    - Commencement (speakers, etc.) (Box 118)
    - Commendations and Congratulations (Box 118)
    - Condolences and Get-Well Wishes (Box 118)
    - Conferences (Box 118)
    - Council of Ten (includes Big Ten), 6 folders (Box 118)
    - D-General (Box 118)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 118)
    - Detroit (Box 118)
    - Detroit Area Pre-College Engineering Program (DAPCEP) (Box 118)
    - Detroit Public Schools (Box 118)
    - Development Council (Box 118)
    - Development Policy Committee (Box 118)
    - Disabled (Box 118)
    - E-General (Box 118)
    - Economic Status of the Faculty, Committee on (CESF) (Box 118)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 118)
    - Education, School of (Box 118)
    - Energy (Box 118)
    - Engineering, College of
      - General (Box 118)
      - Process Metallurgy Laboratory (Box 118)
    - F-General (Box 118)
    - Fees (Box 118)
    - Fellowships, Scholarships, Awards, etc. (Box 118)
    - Financial Aid, Office of, 2 folders (Box 118)
    - Financial Officer, Vice President and Chief (J. Brinkerhoff) (Box 118)
    - Flint Campus Ford Foundation (Box 118)
    - Ford, Gerald R., Library (Box 119)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests (Box 119)
    - G-General (Box 119)
    - Gender Studies, Committee on (Box 119)
    - General Counsel, Office of (Box 119)
    - Graduate Employees Organization (GEO) (Box 119)
    - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of (Box 119)
    - H-General (Box 119)
    - Hazing, 3 folders (Box 119)
    - Heebink, David V. (Assistant to the President) (Box 119)
    - Honorary Degree (Recommendations, etc.) (Box 119)
    - Hospital and Health Care (Box 119)
    - Hospital Breakfast Meetings (Box 119)
    - Housing, 2 folders (Box 119)
    - I-General (Box 119)
    - Indirect Costs, 2 folders (Box 119)
    - Institutes (UM) (Box 119)
    - International (Box 119)
    - Introduction, Letters of (Box 119)
    - Iran/Iranian Students/American Hostages (Box 119)
    - J-General (Box 119)
    - K-General (Box 119)
    - Kellogg Foundation, W.K. (Box 119)
    - L-General (Box 119)
    - Letters from the Public (Box 119)
    - Library, University (Box 119)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 119)
    - M-General (Box 119)
    - Medical School (Box 119)
    - Mellon Foundation, Andrew W. (Box 119)
    - Michigan, State of (Box 120)
      - General (Box 120)
      - Education, Department of (Box 120)
      - Fiscal Agencies (Box 120)
      - Governor's Office (Box 120)
      - Management and Budget, Department of (Box 120)
    - Michigan Historical Collections/Bentley Historical Library (Box 120)
    - Michigan Senators and Representatives (Box 120)
    - Michigan State University (Box 120)
    - Michigan Union (Restructuring), 3 folders (Box 120)
    - Minority Affairs, 3 folders (Box 120)
    - Museum of Art (Box 120)
    - Music, School of (Box 120)
    - N-General (Box 120)
    - National (Box 120)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (Box 120)
    - National Collegiate Athletics Association (NCAA) (Box 120)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 120)
    - O-General (Box 120)
    - P-General (Box 120)
    - Parking (Box 120)
    - Peace Corps 20th Anniversary (10/14/80) (Box 120)
    - Positions
      - Application For (Box 120)
      - Elsewhere (Box 120)
    - Presidents Council of State Colleges and Universities (PCSCU), 6 folders (Box 120)
    - Q-General (Box 120)
    - R-General (Box 120)
    - Rackham Board of Governors (Box 120)
    - Recreational Sports "Significant Other" Policy (Box 120)
    - Regents
      - Baker, Deane (Box 120)
      - Brown, Paul W. (Box 120)
      - Dunn, Gerald R. (Box 120)
      - Laro, David (Box 120)
      - Nederlander, Robert E. (Box 120)
      - Power, Sarah G. (Box 120)
      - Roach, Thomas A. (Box 120)
      - Waters, James L. (Box 121)
      - Varner, Nellie (Box 121)
    - Research, Vice President for ©. Overberger) (Box 121)
    - Research, Recombinant DNA (1975-1981), 4 folders (Box 121)
    - Research Libraries Group (RLG) (Box 121)
    - Rose Bowl (Box 121)
    - ROTC (Reserve Officers Training Corps) (Box 121)
    - S-General (Box 121)
    - Senate, Senate Advisory (SACUA), Senate Assembly (Box 121)
    - Student Government (Box 121)
    - Student Publications (including Michigan Daily) (Box 121)
    - Student Services, Vice President for (Henry Johnson) (Box 121)
    - T-General (Box 121)
    - Title IX (Box 121)
    - U-General (Box 121)
    - Union Activities (Box 121)
    - United States
      - General (Box 121)
      - Education, Department of (Box 121)
      - Labor, Department of (Box 121)
      - Senators and Representatives (Box 121)
      - Transportation, Department of (UM/WSU project) (Box 121)
    - University Relations and Development, Vice President for (Acting Vice President Harold Jacobson) (Box 121)
    - V-General (Box 121)
    - W-General (Box 121)
    - Washtenaw (Box 121)
    - XYZ-General (Box 121)
  - 1981-1982
    - A-General (Box 122)
    - Academic Affairs, Vice President for (Billy Frye) (Box 122)
    - Accreditation (Box 122)
    - Admissions, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - Affirmative Action, Office of (Box 122)
    - Alumni Association (Box 122)
    - American (Box 122)
    - American Council on Education (ACE) (Box 122)
    - American Institutions, Program in (Box 122)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 122)
    - Annenberg Funds (Box 122)
    - Arms Control (Box 122)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU), 3 folders (Box 122)
    - Athletics, 3 folders (Box 122)
    - B-General (Box 122)
    - Bluebonnet Bowl (Box 122)
    - Budget (Box 122)
    - Business-Higher Education Forum (Box 122)
    - C-General (Box 123)
    - Centers (Box 123)
    - Chen, Wen-Chen (Box 123)
    - Clements Library (Box 123)
    - Commencement (Speakers, etc.) (Box 123)
    - Commendations and Congratulations (Box 123)
    - Condolences and Get-Well Wishes (Box 123)
    - Conferences (UM-affiliated), 2 folders (Box 123)
    - Consortium of Social Sciences Associations (COSSA) (Box 123)
    - Council of Ten (includes Big Ten), 5 folders (Box 123)
    - D-General (Box 123)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 123)
    - Detroit (Box 123)
    - Detroit Public Schools (Box 123)
    - Development Council Office (Box 123)
    - Development Policy Committee, 2 folders (Box 123)
    - E-General (Box 123)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 123)
    - Economic Status of the Faculty, Committee on (CESF) (Box 123)
    - Education, School of (Box 123)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 124)
    - English Composition Board (ECB) (Box 124)
    - Enrollment, 2 folders (Box 124)
    - Executive Officers (including retreat), 4 folders (Box 124)
    - F-General (Box 124)
    - Fees (Box 124)
    - Fellowships, Scholarships, Awards, etc (Box 124)
    - Financial Aid, Office of, 2 folders (Box 124)
    - Flint Campus (Box 124)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests (Box 124)
    - G-General (Box 124)
    - General Counsel, Office of (Box 124)
    - General Motors Institute (GMI) (Box 124)
    - Graduate Employees Organization (GEO) (Box 124)
    - H-General (Box 124)
    - Hazing Policy (Box 124)
    - Honorary Degrees (recommendations, etc) (Box 124)
    - Hospital, University (includes McAuley Health Center/Ambulance Service and Breakfast Meetings), 4 folders (Box 125)
    - Housing, 2 folders (Box 125)
    - I-General (Box 125)
    - Independent Business Research Institute of Michigan (Box 125)
    - Indirect Costs, 6 folders (Box 125)
    - Institutes (Box 125)
    - Introduction, Letters of (Box 125)
    - J-General (Box 125)
    - K-General (Box 125)
    - Kellogg Foundation, W. K. (Box 125)
    - Kresge Foundation (Box 125)
    - L-General (Box 125)
    - Law School (Box 125)
    - Letters from Public (Box 125)
    - Library, University (Box 125)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 125)
    - M-General (Box 125)
    - Medical School (includes radiology/nuclear magnetic resonance), 2 folders (Box 125)
    - Michigan, State of
      - General (Box 125)
      - Education, Department of (Box 126)
      - Fiscal Agencies (Box 126)
      - Governor's Office (Box 126)
      - Management and Budget, Department of (Box 126)
    - Michigan Historical Collections/Bentley Historical Library (Box 126)
    - Michigan Research Corporation (Box 126)
    - Michigan Senators and Representatives (Box 126)
    - Michigan Society of Fellows (Box 126)
    - Michigan Tax Study (H. Brazer, includes final report and summary) (Box 126)
    - Minority Affairs (Box 126)
    - Molecular Biology Institute Task Force, 2 folders (Box 126)
    - N-General (Box 126)
    - National (Box 126)
    - National Academy of Sciences (10/81 meeting) (Box 126)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (Box 126)
    - National Collegiate Athletics Association (NCAA) (Box 126)
    - O-General (Box 126)
    - Ochberg, Frank (Box 126)
    - P-General (Box 126)
    - Positions
      - Application For (Box 126)
      - Elsewhere (Box 126)
    - Presidents Council of State Colleges and Universities (PCSCU), 6 folders (Box 127)
    - Presidents Group, Michigan Higher Education Institutions (Box 127)
    - Q-General (Box 127)
    - R-General (Box 127)
    - Regents
      - Baker, Deane (Box 127)
      - Brown, Paul W. (Box 127)
      - Dunn, Gerald R. (Box 127)
      - Nederlander, Robert E. (Box 127)
      - Power, Sarah G. (Box 127)
      - Varner, Nellie M. (Box 127)
    - Research, Vice President for ©. Overberger), 2 folders (Box 127)
    - Research Agenda (Box 127)
    - Retirement (Box 127)
    - ROTC (Reserve Officers Training Corps) (Box 127)
    - S-General (Box 127)
    - Senate, Senate Advisory (SACUA), Senate Assembly (Box 127)
    - Song, Jiakun (Box 127)
    - Student Services, Vice President for (Henry Johnson) (Box 127)
    - T-General (Box 127)
    - Tappan Hall (Box 127)
    - Telecommunications (Box 127)
    - Title IX (Box 127)
    - U-General (Box 127)
    - United States
      - General (Box 127)
      - Education, Department of (Box 127)
      - Senators and Representatives (Box 127)
    - University Relations and Development, Vice President for (Acting Vice President Harold Jacobson) (Box 127)
    - V-General (Box 127)
    - W-General (Box 127)
    - XYZ-General (Box 127)
  - 1982-1983
    - A-General (Box 128)
    - Academic Affairs, Vice President for (Billy Frye) (Box 128)
    - Academic Affairs Advisory Council (AAAC) (Box 128)
    - Accreditation (Box 128)
    - Admissions, 2 folders (Box 128)
    - Affirmative Action, Office of (Box 128)
    - Alumni Association (Box 128)
    - American (Box 128)
    - American Council on Education (ACE) (Box 128)
    - American Institutions, Program in (Box 128)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 128)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU), 3 folders (Box 128)
    - Athletics (includes academic admission standards and scheduling, and Crisler Arena), 3 folders (Box 128)
    - B-General (Box 128)
    - Budget (Box 128)
    - Business-Higher Education Forum (Box 128)
    - C-General (Box 128)
    - Capital Needs (Box 128)
    - Centers (Box 128)
    - Clements Library (Box 128)
    - Commencement (speakers, etc.) (Box 128)
    - Commendations and Congratulations (Box 129)
    - Computers (Box 129)
    - Condolences and Get-Well Wishes (Box 129)
    - Conferences, 7 folders (Box 129)
    - Council of Ten (includes Big Ten), 3 folders (Box 129)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC) (Box 129)
    - D-General (Box 129)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 129)
    - Detroit Public Schools (Box 129)
    - Development Council Office (Box 129)
    - Development and University Relations, Vice President for (Acting Vice President Harold Jacobson) (Box 129)
    - Development Policy Committee, 3 folders
      - folders 1-2 (Box 129)
      - folder 3 (Box 130)
    - E (General) (Box 130)
    - Economic Alliance for Michigan (Box 130)
    - Economic Status of the Faculty, Committee on the (CESF) (Box 130)
    - Education, School of (Box 130)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 130)
    - Enrollment, 2 folders (Box 130)
    - Executive Officers, 2 folders (Box 130)
    - F-General (Box 130)
    - Fees (Box 130)
    - Fellowships, Scholarships, Awards, etc. (Box 130)
    - Financial Aid, Office of, 2 folders (Box 130)
    - Flint Campus (Box 130)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests (Box 130)
    - G-General (Box 130)
    - General Counsel, Office of (Box 130)
    - Graduate Employees Organization (GEO) (Box 130)
    - Graduate School Doctoral Program Rankings (Box 130)
    - H-General (Box 130)
    - Honorary Degrees (Recommendations, etc.) (Box 130)
    - Hospital (Box 130)
    - Hospital Breakfast Meetings (Box 130)
    - Housing, 2 folders (Box 131)
    - I (General) (Box 131)
    - Indirect Costs, 2 folders (Box 131)
    - Institutes (Box 131)
    - Introduction, Letters of (Box 131)
    - J-General (Box 131)
    - K-General (Box 131)
    - L-General (Box 131)
    - Library, University (Box 131)
    - M-General (Box 131)
    - Medical School (Box 131)
    - Michigan Awareness Program (Box 131)
    - Michigan, State of
      - General (Box 131)
      - Education, Department of (Box 131)
      - Fiscal Agencies (Box 131)
      - Governor's Office (Box 131)
      - Management and Budget, Department of (Box 131)
    - Michigan Historical Collections/Bentley Historical Library (Box 131)
    - Michigan Research Corporation (Box 131)
    - Michigan Senators and Representatives (Box 131)
    - Minority Affairs
      - General (Box 131)
      - Trotter House (Box 131)
    - Molecular Biology Institute Task Force, 2 folders (Box 131)
    - Music, School of (Box 131)
    - N-General (Box 131)
    - National (Box 131)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (Box 131)
    - National Collegiate Athletics Association (NCAA) (Box 132)
    - O-General (Box 132)
    - P-General (Box 132)
    - Phi Eta Sigma (Box 132)
    - Positions
      - Applications for (Box 132)
      - Elsewhere (Box 132)
    - Presidents' Council of State Colleges and Universities (PCSCU) (Box 132)
    - Presidents' Group (Michigan Higher Education Institutions) (Box 132)
    - Q-General (Box 132)
    - R-General (Box 132)
    - Rackham Board of Governors (Box 132)
    - Rankings, Academic (Box 132)
    - Regents
      - Retreat (7/82) (Box 132)
      - Baker, Deane (Box 132)
      - Brown, Paul W. (Box 132)
      - Dunn, Gerald R. (Box 132)
      - Nederlander, Robert E. (Box 132)
      - Power, Sarah G. (Box 132)
      - Roach, Thomas A. (Box 132)
      - Varner, Nellie M. (Box 132)
      - Waters, James L. (Box 132)
    - Research, Vice President for ©. Overberger)
      - General (Box 132)
      - Small Business Innovation Act (Box 132)
      - Integrity of Scholarship (Box 132)
    - Retirement (Box 132)
    - ROTC (Reserve Officers Training Corps) (Box 132)
    - S-General (Box 132)
    - Scholarships, Bentley (Box 132)
    - Senate, Senate Advisory (SACUA), Senate Assembly (Box 132)
    - State Relations, Vice President for (Richard Kennedy) (Box 132)
    - Student Government (Box 132)
    - Student Publications (includes Michigan Daily) (Box 132)
    - T-General (Box 132)
    - Taubman, A. Alfred (Box 132)
    - Telecommunications (Box 132)
    - Title IX (Box 132)
    - U-General (Box 132)
    - Union Activities (Box 132)
    - United States (Box 133)
      - General (Box 133)
      - Education, Department of (Box 133)
      - Senators and Representatives (Box 133)
    - V-General (Box 133)
    - W-General (Box 133)
    - Wayne State University (Box 133)
    - XYZ-General (Box 133)
  - 1983-1984
    - A-General (Box 133)
    - Academic Affairs, Vice President for and Provost (Billy Frye) (Box 133)
    - Accreditation (Box 133)
    - Admissions, 2 folders (Box 133)
    - Affirmative Action, Office of (Box 133)
    - Alumni Association (Box 133)
    - American (Box 133)
    - American Institutions, Program in (Box 133)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 133)
    - Ann Arbor Area Presidents (Box 133)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU), 3 folders (Box 133)
    - Athletics
      - General (Box 133)
      - Academic Admission Standards (Box 133)
    - Awards (Box 133)
    - B-General (Box 133)
    - Budget, 2 folders (Box 134)
    - Business-Higher Education Forum (Box 134)
    - C-General (Box 134)
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York (Box 134)
    - Centers (Box 134)
    - Clements Library (Box 134)
    - Commencement (speakers, etc.) (Box 134)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC) (Box 134)
    - Computers (Box 134)
    - Condolences and Get-Well Wishes (Box 134)
    - Conferences (Box 134)
    - Congratulations and Commendations (Box 134)
    - Consortium of Social Science Associations (COSSA) (Box 134)
    - Council of Ten (includes Big Ten) (Box 134)
    - D-General (Box 134)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 135)
    - Detroit Public Schools (Box 135)
    - Detroit Public Schools/UM Symposium (6/84) (Box 135)
    - Development and Communications, Vice President for (Jon Cosovich) (Box 135)
    - Development Policy Committee, 2 folders (Box 135)
    - E-General (Box 135)
    - Economic Future of the Great Lakes State, Congress of (Box 135)
    - Energy (Box 135)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 135)
    - Enrollment (Box 135)
    - Executive Officers (Box 135)
    - Executive Officers' Enrollment Retreat (10/83) (Box 135)
    - F-General (Box 135)
    - Fellowships
      - General (Box 135)
      - Journalist in Residence (Box 135)
    - Financial Aid, Office of, 2 folders (Box 135)
    - Financial Aid-Solomon Amendment (Box 135)
    - Financial Officer, Vice President and Chief (J. Brinkerhoff) (Box 135)
    - Flint Campus (Box 135)
    - G-General (Box 136)
    - General Counsel, Office of (Box 136)
    - Graduate Employees Organization (GEO) (Box 136)
    - Graduate Studies and Research, Interim Vice President for (Alfred Sussman) (Box 136)
    - H-General (Box 136)
    - Haig, Alexander (Box 136)
    - Honorary Degrees (recommendations, etc.) (Box 136)
    - Hospital, University (Box 136)
    - Hospital Breakfast Meetings, 3 folders (Box 136)
    - Housing, 2 folders (Box 136)
    - I-General (Box 136)
    - Indirect Costs/A-21 (Box 136)
    - Institutes (Box 136)
    - Introduction, Letters of (Box 136)
    - Investments (Box 136)
    - J-General (Box 136)
    - K-General (Box 136)
    - Kung, Hans (Visiting Professor) (Box 136)
    - L-General (Box 136)
    - Library, University (Box 136)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 136)
    - M-General (Box 137)
    - Medical Center
      - General (Box 137)
      - Reorganization (Box 137)
    - Medical School (Box 137)
    - Mellon Foundation, Andrew W. (Box 137)
    - Michigan, State of
      - Commerce, Department of (Brazer Michigan economy study) (Box 137)
      - Education, Department of (Box 137)
      - Governor's Office (Box 137)
      - Governor's Commission on the Future of Higher Education, 3 folders (Box 137)
      - Management and Budget, Department of (Box 137)
    - Michigan Research Corporation (Box 137)
    - Michigan Senators and Representatives (Box 137)
    - Michigan Society of Fellows (Box 137)
    - Michigan, Special Medical Task Force (Box 137)
    - Michigan Today (Box 137)
    - Michigan Union (Restructuring) (Box 137)
    - Minority Affairs (Box 137)
    - Molecular Biology Institute (Box 137)
    - Mullen, Albert P. (Box 138)
    - Musical Society, University (UMS) (Box 138)
    - N-General (Box 138)
    - National (Box 138)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (Box 138)
    - National Collegiate Athletics Association (NCAA) (Box 138)
    - National Council on International Research and Man Power (Box 138)
    - National Institutes of Health (AAU/NASULGC/ACE meeting 7/8/83) (Box 138)
    - Nigerian Students (financial problems) (Box 138)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 138)
    - O-General (Box 138)
    - P-General (Box 138)
    - Parking Operations (Box 138)
    - Plant Extension (Box 138)
    - Positions
      - Applications For (Box 138)
      - Elsewhere (Box 138)
    - Presidents' Council of State Colleges and Universities (PCSCU), 4 folders (Box 138)
    - Presidents' Group, Michigan Higher Education Institutions (Box 138)
    - Q-General (Box 138)
    - R-General (Box 138)
    - Rackham Board of Governors, 4 folders (Box 138)
    - Regents (Box 139)
      - Baker, Deane (Box 139)
      - Brown, Paul W. (Box 139)
      - Dunn, Gerald R. (Box 139)
      - Nederlander, Robert E. (Box 139)
      - Power, Sarah G. (Box 139)
      - Roach, Thomas A. (Box 139)
      - Varner, Nellie M. (Box 139)
      - Waters, James L. (Box 139)
    - Research (Box 139)
    - Research-Integrity of Scholarship (Box 139)
    - Research Libraries Group (RLG) (Box 139)
    - Retirement (Box 139)
    - ROTC (Reserve Officers Training Corps) (Box 139)
    - S-General (Box 139)
    - Scholarships
      - General (Box 139)
      - Bentley (Box 139)
    - Senate, Senate Advisory (SACUA), Senate Assembly (Box 139)
    - Student Government (Box 139)
    - Student Publications (includes Michigan Daily) (Box 139)
    - Student Services, Vice President for (Henry Johnson) (Box 139)
    - Supercomputers (Box 139)
    - T-General (Box 139)
    - Taubman, A. Alfred (Box 139)
    - Tax Equity and Fiscal Responsibility Act (TEFRA) (Box 139)
    - Telecommunications (Box 139)
    - Title IX (Box 139)
    - U-General (Box 139)
    - Union Activities (Box 139)
    - United States
      - General (Box 139)
      - Education, Department of (Box 139)
      - Senators and Representatives (Box 139)
    - V-General (Box 139)
    - W-General (Box 139)
    - XYZ-General (Box 139)
  - 1984-1985
    - A-General (Box 140)
    - Academic Affairs, Vice President for and Provost (Billy Frye) (Box 140)
    - Academic Affairs Advisory Council (AAAC) (Box 140)
    - Accreditation (Box 140)
    - Admissions, 2 folders (Box 140)
    - Affirmative Action, Office of (Box 140)
    - Alumni Association (Box 140)
    - American (Box 140)
    - American Council on Education (ACE) (Box 140)
    - American Institutions, Program in (Box 140)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 140)
    - Arms Control (Box 140)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU), 2 folders (Box 140)
    - Athletics (Box 140)
    - Awards (Box 140)
    - B-General (Box 140)
    - Ballot Proposals (Box 140)
    - Budget, 2 folders (Box 140)
    - Business-Higher Education Forum (Box 140)
    - C-General (Box 141)
    - Campus Compact (Project for Public and Community Service) (Box 141)
    - Centers (Box 141)
    - Commencement (speakers, etc) (Box 141)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC) (Box 141)
    - Condolences and Get-Well Wishes (Box 141)
    - Conferences, 4 folders (Box 141)
    - Congratulations and Commendations (Box 141)
    - Council of Ten (includes Big Ten) (Box 141)
    - D-General (Box 141)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 141)
    - Detroit Public Schools (Box 141)
    - Development and University Relations, Vice President for (Jon Cosovich) (Box 141)
    - Development Policy Committee, 2 folders (Box 141)
    - E-General (Box 142)
    - Economic Alliance for Michigan (Box 142)
    - Economic Status of the Faculty, Committee on the (CESF) (Box 142)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 142)
    - Enrollment (Box 142)
    - Executive Officers (Box 142)
    - F-General (Box 142)
    - Fees (Box 142)
    - Fellowships
      - General (Box 142)
      - Journalist in Resident (Box 142)
    - Financial Aid, Office of, 2 folders (Box 142)